{
    "id": "137964c4dfeb4998aa87270ba4f074de",
    "title": "Subject-Verb Agreement Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There ………………… many objections to the plan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d38aa7807b0745d18f52715cc8614452"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither his father nor his mother ……………….. alive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b5871c576d8417eb6ff4620d6f80f54"
        },
        {
            "question": "Iron as well as gold ………………… found in India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ac70b19320db4d81b8e4f2aaeb6ea6fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "No news ……………….. good news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "633ee8f7a80f4b29bb91598190cd75b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The great poet and novelist ………………. dead.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "is",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f9cdfb41d1d94da2bb4ebaf17bd0a6d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of these umbrellas ……………… yours?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "is",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec5d13e2f4be42f88af2d4f878da2b15"
        },
        {
            "question": "Every leaf and every flower …………….. stripped off the tree.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7fc4f0c05ab454ea60141070d319717"
        },
        {
            "question": "Milton is one of the greatest poets who ………………. ever lived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3619f3b59c6548aaa9d29b7cd0808045"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dacoit and his followers ……………… escaped.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "95b357b741254f86b65511a41523cf8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "None of you ………………. done the work correctly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7563ea6568cb4763af2e30a271efa98d"
        }
    ]
}